Finding Aid for the Will Connell Papers LSC.0893
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Miscellaneous views and portraits., Mounted prints, 45 × 35.5cm., unless otherwise noted. Chiefly untitled. (Box 20)
  - 4. Close-up of woman holding steering wheel of a car while her scarf is blowing in the wind, 1933. (Box 20)
  - 5. Close-up portrait of woman wearing a white cloche hat, pearls, and dotted dress, 1932. (Box 20)
  - 6. Right profile of woman in no.5, 1932. (Box 20)
  - 7. Close-up portrait of man in dark suit with striped tie, 1931. (Box 20)
  - 8. Portrait of older man holding a pipe, 1932. (Box 20)
  - 9. Portrait of young man in light colored suit, 1928. (Box 20)
  - 10. Portrait of man in flecked suit smoking a cigarette, 1930. (Box 20)
  - 11. Portrait of man with little girl sitting on his knee, 1930. (Box 20)
  - 12. Portrait of a woman in black dress sitting on a bench, n.d. ( (Box 20)
  - 13. Close-up portrait of woman looking over her shoulder, 1929. (Box 20)
  - 14. At the Concert, 1926. (Box 20)
  - 15. Mother & Son, 1929. (Box 20)
  - 16. Portrait of Jane, the Sunkist baby, 1933. (Box 20)
  - 17. Jane, 1933.; (Enlarged close-up, different pose from no.16: 43.3 × 35.5cm.) [Lower right-hand corner of mount damaged]. (Box 20)
  - 18. Janet, Same child as in no.16-17, despite name discrepancy., n.d.; (Enlargement of no.17: 48.4 × 38cm.). (Box 20)
  - 19. Will Connell. Photograph by Fred Dupprich was exhibited Members Salon of Camera Pictorialists of Los Angeles, 1933. (Box 20)
  - 20. Portrait of a lady in Spanish costume, Photograph won an Honorable Mention in the Eighth Annual Competition of American Photography, 1928. 1928. (Box 20)
  - 21. Metal dishes (silver? pewter?), 1929. (Box 20)
  - 22. Rain Pattern, 1931.; (43 × 35.5cm.). (Box 20)
    (See also Box 13)
  - 23. Coast at the foot of Topanga Canyon, 1926. (Box 20)
  - 24. Raising the tent, 1926. (Box 20)
  - 25. Glass of orange juice, Sunkist ad., 1928. (Box 20)
  - 26. Diffusers for oil pumps, 1931.; [Remounted and over-matted for exhibit, 1976]. (Box 20)
  - 27. Lighthouse, Pt. Magu, 1928.; [Remounted and over-matted for exhibit, 1976]. (Box 20)
  - 28-29. Model in bra and panty girdle in front of vanity mirror, 1938.; (no.29 undated, 46 × 35.5cm.) [Damaged photographs]. (Box 20)
    (See also Box 19 and 28)
  - 30. #3, Hosiery ad(?)., 1938.; [Damaged photograph]. (Box 20)
  - 31. Donald Herold, 1931. (Box 20)
- Miscellaneous unidentified views, n.d.; Various sizes, chiefly unmounted. (Box 21)
  - 1-3. Montage of farm life with cows and man driving a tractor in the foreground., (3 copies, 36.5 × 41.5cm.). (Box 21)
  - 4-5. Giant wave crashing on rocks., (Duplicate copies: 40.5 × 41.5cm.). (Box 21)
  - 6-7. Unfinished montage of forrest, beach and aeriel view of an island., (Duplicate copies: 40.5 × 50.5cm.). (Box 21)
  - 8. Mountain range., (32.5 × 38.3cm.) [This is a cropped photograph and appears to have been cut in half unevenly]. (Box 21)
  - 9. Montage of beach, wave, mountains, and forest., (Utilizes no.6-8; 40.3 × 50.5cm.). (Box 21)
  - 10. Unfinished montage of golfers and polo players., (40.3 × 50.5cm.). (Box 21)
  - 11-14. Rocky hill with solitary tree overlooking a lake(?) or ocean(?)., (4 copies: 27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 21)
  - 15. Unfinished montage of beach scene., (27.2 × 35.6cm.) [This is a cropped photograph]. (Box 21)
  - 16. Unifinished montage of beach scene, sailboats, and mountains., (no.15 is part of this photo; 27.7 × 35.5cm.) [This is a cropped photograph]. (Box 21)
  - 17. Two cars on highway, 1920s.; (25 × 17cm.). (Box 21)
  - 18. Fishermen pulling in net., (24 × 40.4cm.). (Box 21)
  - 19. Sports, Montage of California athletic events., 1939.; (Utilizes no.10, no.15, no.16; mounted: 38 × 61cm.). (Box 21)
  - 20. Missions, Montage of California Missions., 1939.; (Mounted: 37.3 × 61cm.). (Box 21)
    (See also Box 4)
  - 21. Black workman wearing protective glasses, 1953.; (Mounted: 58 × 48.3cm.). (Box 21)
  - 22. Airplane wings at Douglas plant(?) Haloid Press Bromide process., (Dry-mounted on extra-heaby board: 61 × 49.3cm.). (Box 21)
    (See also Box 2)
  - 23. Nescafé ad - Joan Davis, [Surface of photograph is damaged and mount chipped. Trimmed to prevent further damage. Original measurements: 60.6 × 51cm.; trimmed: 47 × 40cm.]. (Box 21)
    (See also Box 24)
  - 24. Knock-out' - for Erwin Wasey Company, 1937.; [Mount chipped. Trimmed to prevent further damage. Original measurements: 61 × 68.5cm.; trimmed: 40.5 × 55cm.]. (Box 21)
    (See also Box 7)
  - 25. Refinery Tower(?)., [Mount chipped. Trimmed to prevent further damage. Original measurements: 63.4 × 51cm.; trimmed: 55.2 × 40.5cm.]. (Box 21)
  - 26. Lemon Juice for Colds' - Sunkist, Man sneezing; blue-toned photo., 1937.; [Mount chipped. Trimmed to prevent further damage. Original measurements: 61 × 68.5cm.; trimmed: 44.5 × 54.7cm.]. (Box 21)
    (See also Box 38)
  - 27. #20 Alamitos St., Long Beach, 76 refinery., n.d.; [Chipped mat, can not be trimmed: 51 × 62cm.]. (Box 21)
  - 28. Train yard scene, 1929.; (Mounted: 45.5 × 35.5cm.) [Overmatted for exhibit, 1976]. (Box 21)
  - 29. Barker Brothers boxes, 1929.; (Mounted: 45.5 × 35.5cm.) [Overmatted for exhibit, 1976]. (Box 21)
- Animal portraits., n.d.; Unmounted prints, 35.5 × 28cm., unless otherwise noted. (Box 22)
- Advertisement photographs. Mainly untitled, n.d.; Unmounted, 35 × 27.5cm., unless otherwise noted. (Box 22)
  - 1-2. Hippopotamus., (2 photos, front and rear views; 24.5 × 19.5cm.). (Box 22)
  - 3. Monkey on perch. (Box 22)
  - 4. Boston terrier puppies., (28 × 35cm.). (Box 22)
  - 5-6. Mother dog licking puppy., (2 copies, 28 × 35cm.). (Box 22)
  - 7-8. Wire-haired terrier., (2 copies, 26 × 34cm.). (Box 22)
  - 9-12. Pekinese with orchid., (3 photos; various sizes; no.12 different pose). (Box 22)
  - 13. Springer spaniel(?)., (28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 22)
  - 14. Scotch terrier. (Box 22)
  - 15-16. His Family Tree, Kitten in front of parent's portrait., 1929.; (25 × 20cm.). (Box 22)
    (See also Box 14)
  - 17. Eagle with spread wings. (Box 22)
  - 18-19. Bird [eagle(?)] with spread wings on rock., (2 copies; special effect). (Box 22)
  - 20-22. Turkey perched on hatchet, side view., (3 copies, 20 × 25cm.). (Box 22)
  - 23-24. Turkey next to stump with hatchet, close-up view., (2 copies, different sizes). (Box 22)
  - 25-26. Turkey behind stump with hatchet., (2 copies, different sizes). (Box 22)
  - 27. Turkey in front of fence, side view. (Box 22)
  - 28-29. Talking turkey. Close-up profiles of turkey, both sides., (no.38: 34 × 26.5cm.). (Box 22)
  - 30. Turkey on U.S. Mail box., (32 × 26.5cm.). (Box 22)
  - 31. Crowing rooster on U.S. Mail box., (33.5 × 26cm. Special effect). (Box 22)
  - 32-34. Marionette puppets. (Box 22)
    (See also Box 23)
    - 32. Hayden Trio. Side rear view. (Box 22)
    - 33. Hayden Trio. Front view. (Box 22)
    - 34. Clown and puppeteer. (Box 22)
  - 35-37. Early theater photographs. (Box 22)
    - 35. Backstage; shadow of man on wall. (Box 22)
    - 36. Backstage; wings. (Box 22)
    - 37. Backstage crew. (Box 22)
  - 38-61. Flower arrangements. Used as illustrations for book: Flower arrangements, by Gregory Conway (a florist), 1940. (Box 22)
    - 48-49. Flower arrangements., (2 photographs, duplicates from above group). (Box 22)
    - 52-56. Flower arrangements., (Mounted, 35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 22)
      - 52. February (Box 22)
      - 53. December. (Box 22)
      - 54. April. (Box 22)
    - 57-58. Flower arrangements., (Mounted, 28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 22)
      - 57. March. (Box 22)
      - 58-61. January., (no.22-24: Unmounted duplicates of no.21). (Box 22)
  - 62-74. Mannings Coffee advertisements. (Box 22)
    - 62. Workers on plantation., (27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 22)
    - 63-65. Canning process., (3 copies). (Box 22)
    - 66-67. Mannings Coffee V.I.P., (2 copies). (Box 22)
    - 68. Roasting coffee beans. (Box 22)
    - 69-72. Testing coffee beans., (no.34-35, duplicates; 27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 22)
    - 73. Woman drinking Mannings coffee., (35.5 × 27cm.). (Box 22)
    - 74. Mock-up of ad: woman drinking coffee, superimposed over typewriter., (21 × 24.5cm.). (Box 22)
  - 75-87. Miscellaneous food advertisements. (Box 22)
    - 75. Candy ad., (26 × 21cm.). (Box 22)
    - 76-77. Avocado and fruit slices., (2 copies, different sizes). (Box 22)
    - 78-79. Avocado slices on lettuce., (2 photos, different views and sizes). (Box 22)
    - 80-81. Avocado halves., (2 photos, different views and sizes). (Box 22)
    - 82. Fruit salad., (27 × 34cm.). (Box 22)
    - 83. Fried egg and bacon., (27.5 × 37.5cm.). (Box 22)
    - 84. Egg in egg cup; angle shot., (27.5 × 37.5cm.). (Box 22)
    - 85. Hands slicing tomato., (28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 22)
    - 86. Melted cheese on toast., (27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 22)
    - 87. Bread and ham., (22 × 18cm.). (Box 22)
  - 88-100. Sunkist ads. (Box 22)
    - 88. Cut lemons over glasses., (36 × 28cm.). (Box 22)
    - 89-92. Glasses of Lemonade on tray., (Different views, no.3-5 duplicates, no.5: 29 × 23.5cm.). (Box 22)
    - 93. Juice extractor/juice bar., (24.5 × 23.5cm.). (Box 22)
    - 94-95. Glass of lemonade on tray., (2 copies, no.7 entitled Design for Prohibitionists.). (Box 22)
    - 96. Glass of juice on background of oranges., (29.5 × 24cm.). (Box 22)
    - 97-98. Glass of juice in bowl of crushed ice., (2 copies, no.11: 29.5 × 24.5cm.). (Box 22)
    - 99. Two women, one with juice., (27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 22)
    - 100. Row of deserts made from oranges., (21.5 × 25cm.). (Box 22)
  - 101-107. Mission Dry and other drinks. (Box 22)
    - 101. Mission Dry Orange drink. Angle view. (Box 22)
    - 102-103. Mission Dry bottles and fruit., (2 copies, different sizes). (Box 22)
    - 104. Mission Dry Orange drink and champagne glass., (35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 22)
    - 105. Mission Dry drinks, various flavors. (Box 22)
    - 106. California Nugget Champagne ad., (21.5 × 19.5cm.). (Box 22)
    - 107. Johnny Walker Red Label scotch whiskey ad. (Box 22)
- Advertisement photographs. Untitled, n.d.; Unmounted, 35.5 × 27cm., unless otherwise noted. (Box 23)
- Los Angeles and vicinity., Unmounted, mainly 35.5 × 27cm., unless otherwise noted. No dates given. (Box 23)
- Miscellaneous untitled scenic photographs, chiefly California. Mostly, n.d.; Unmounted, various sizes. (Box 23)
  - 1-20. Ice and its uses. (Box 23)
    - 1. Block of ice., (29 × 23.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 2-3. Ice cubes in wine glasses., (2 copies, no.11: 26 × 28cm.). (Box 23)
    - 4-5. Half cantaloupe in crushed ice., (2 copies, 33 × 24.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 6-8. Ward ice-box demonstration., (3 copies, different sizes). (Box 23)
    - 9. Ward ice-box demonstration., (25 × 20cm.). (Box 23)
    - 10-11. Ward ice-box on globe ad., (2 copies, different sizes). (Box 23)
    - 12-17. Ward ice-box demonstration., (6 copies, 27.5 × 25.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 18. Open ice-box. (Box 23)
    - 19. Open ice-box with drop tray added. (Box 23)
    - 20. Closed ice-box., (36 × 28cm.). (Box 23)
  - 21-30. Children. (Box 23)
    - 21. Sleeping girl. (Box 23)
    - 22. Little boy eating candy(?). (Box 23)
    - 23-24. Little boy drinking from cup., (2 copies, slight variation in cups). (Box 23)
    - 25. Little girl drinking from cup. Rear angle view. (Box 23)
    - 26-27. Little boy lifted in air by a man. (Different men, different poses). (Box 23)
    - 28. Little girl and puppy., (Special effect photo). (Box 23)
    - 29. Young boy on bicycle. (Box 23)
    - 30. Young girl Christmas gift shopping. (Box 23)
  - 31. Collage. Wastepaper basket overflowing with trash, 1952. (Box 23)
  - 32-34. Christmas tree., (3 copies). (Box 23)
  - 35. Hen and chickens. Cactus and two offshoots. (Box 23)
  - 36-39. Hollywood Turf Club., (Different views; no.1-2: 26 × 35cm., no.3: 28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 40-42. Los Angeles Department store., (3 copies; no.5: 15 × 32.5cm., no.6-7: 27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 23)
  - 43-44. Farmers' Market., (2 views, 27 × 34cm.). (Box 23)
  - 45. Freeway construction, Los Angeles Civic Center., (28 × 35cm.). (Box 23)
  - 46-59. Los Angeles in the rain., (Various views, many duplicates; various sizes). (Box 23)
  - 60-61. Cars on a street at night., (2 copies, 20.5 × 25.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 62. Men walking under tunnel at Hope Street. (Box 23)
  - 63-67. Miscellaneous pedestrian scenes., (Various sizes). (Box 23)
  - 68. Woman in beauty shop. (Box 23)
  - 69-71. Montages of California camp life., (2 photos, different views, 27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 23)
  - 72. Montage of California scene, with map drawn in blue., (37.5 × 28.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 73. Rocky stream bed, three trees, (High Sierra country?)., n.d.; (32 × 18.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 74-82. Big Bear, California, n.d.; (Various scenes, some duplicates; mainly 27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 83-85. Sierra Nevada Mountains. Raineir(?) Shasta(?)., (2 copies, different sizes). (Box 23)
  - 86-87. Winter scene in the Sierra high country., (Duplicates, 35 × 27cm.). (Box 23)
  - 88-89. Summer scene in the Sierra high country., (Duplicates, 35 × 27cm.). (Box 23)
  - 90. Mohave desert, view of southern end of Sierras., (35 × 27cm.). (Box 23)
  - 91. Cactus branch., (35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 92-93. Pomona College, Pomona, California., (2 views, 27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 23)
  - 94. Avalon Harbor., (26.5 × 34.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 95. San Francisco Harbor., (27 × 34.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 96-99. Storm over the Central Valley., (Several views, 35.5 × 28cm., except no.27: 28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 100. Relief map of California., (26 × 34cm.). (Box 23)
  - 101. Desert Tragedy, Remains of horse-drawn buggy., 1925.; (17.5 × 23cm.). (Box 23)
  - 102. Donner Pass--April, 1927.; (28 × 35cm.). (Box 23)
  - 103-104. Sylmar/Techacapi foothills(?)., (2 copies, 27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 23)
  - 105-110. Grand Canyon; aerial views with clouds filling the Canyon., (Some duplicates, various sizes). (Box 23)
  - 111. Swimming pool and swimmers., (35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 112. People dining on patio, 1920's.; (35 × 28cm.). (Box 23)
  - 113. Louis & Grace, 1926.; (32 × 21.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 114. Picture of Saint (Virgin Mary?) in an ornate frame., (34.5 × 27cm.). (Box 23)
  - 115-120. Nudes. (Box 23)
    - 115-116. Standing nude facing cliff., (Duplicate photos, 35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 117. Seated nude embracing knees by side of cliff. Side view., (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 118. Nude on pile of rocks. Front view., (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 119. Nude resting head and arms against rock. Side view., (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 120. Nude, head bent, walking downhill on path along cliff. Side view., (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 121. Flintridge Golf Course, aerial view., (35 × 27cm.). (Box 23)
  - 122-130. Orange groves, Porterville, California. (Box 23)
    - 122-125. Views of farmhouses and groves., (4 photos, no.18 and no.19 are duplicates; (28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 126-127. Crop spraying (insecticide), (Duplicates; 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
    - 128-130. Picking oranges., (3 copies; 35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 131-135. Orange groves, Calabasas, California., (5 photos; various views, some duplicates; various sizes.). (Box 23)
  - 136. Poinsettia fields, Encinitas, California., (35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 23)
  - 137. Burpee flower field near San Diego with beehive for cross-pollenation., (27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 138. Cottonfield in the San Joacin Valley, man on tractor super-imposed (trick effect)., (28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 139. Man on tractor in cottonfield. (Same view as no.34 without trick effect)., (28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 140. Furrows of earth. Close-up view., (28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
  - 141-146. Miscellaneous mountain views., (All 35.5 × 28cm, except no.42: 28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 23)
- Miscellaneous color photographs: Rejects & Duplicates., Unmounted, mainly 35.5 × 27cm., unless otherwise noted. (Box 24)
  - 1-2. Woman in long dress standing by blue car., Carbro print (2 copies; no.1: 25 × 29cm., no.2: 35 × 28cm.). (Box 24)
  - 3. Girl singing into CBS mike., Dye print (34 × 24.5cm). (Box 24)
    (See also Box 29)
  - 4. Burpee Seed Farm, Lompoc Valley, California, 1938.; Dye print (27 × 35cm.). (Box 24)
  - 5. California poppies in a field of purple lupin and buttercups, 1938.; (35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 6-7. Alfalfa, Smiling pose., 1938.; Dye print (Duplicates). (Box 24)
  - 8. Alfalfa, Serious pose, head in hand., 1938.; Carbro print. (Box 24)
  - 9-12. Display of various magazines., (4 photos, no.9-10: 33 × 35cm., no.11-12: 35.5 × 28cm., dye prints, using 3 exposures). (Box 24)
  - 13. Jars of chemicals on shelves, n.d.; (35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 24)
  - 14. Display of Eckoware pots with Christmas decorations., Probably a blow-up from a small negative (35mm?) (20 × 30cm.). (Box 24)
  - 15. Dimples of Hughes Place, 1937. Close-up of cow's face., Carbro print (27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 16-18. Close-up of cow's face., (3 copies. Untitled duplicates of no.15; dye prints, 27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 19-20. Close-up of cow's face., (2 copies. Same as no.15-18, different paper; dye prints, 26.5 × 33cm.). (Box 24)
  - 21. Lompoc flower fields, (Burpee?)., n.d.; Carbro print (27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 22-24. Cluster of grapes on vine, 1937.; Dye print (3 copies, 35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 24)
  - 25-28. Cluster of grapes on vine, 1937.; (4 copies; different views from no.22-24; 35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 24)
  - 29-31. Fruit salad in blue bowl., Carbro print (3 copies; 25.5 × 30.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 32-33. Mickey Rooney in Out West with the Hardy's., Dye print(?) (2 copies, 35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 24)
  - 34-35. Model(?) being fitted for gown, n.d.; Dye print(?) (2 copies). (Box 24)
  - 36. Sidewalk design at Clifton's Brookdale Cafeteria., Dye print (27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 37. Sidewalk design at Clifton's Brookdale Cafeteria., Carbro print. (Duplicate of no.36 except different colors; 27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 38-39. Sidewalk design at Clifton's Brookdale Cafeteria., Dye prints. (2 copies; different view from no.36-37; 27.5 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 40. Woman in hat entering car., Dye print(?) (17 × 28cm.). (Box 24)
  - 41. Man standing behind green car., Dye print(?) (14 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 42. Woman's face, double exposure attempt., (11 × 8.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 43-44. Clouds., (Duplicate scenes, but different colors; dye prints; 16.5 × 21.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 45. Flowers at Reinelt & Vetterle Nursery, Capitola, California, 1937. (Box 24)
  - 46. Blonde model in red print dress., Carbro print. (Box 24)
  - 47. Couple in evening dress. Cigarette ad(?)., Carbro print (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 48. Mother, holding pussywillows, and child, holding toy, on steps of home in San Marino, California., Dye print. (Box 24)
  - 49-50. Mother, holding basket of flowers, and child, 1936.; Dye print. (2 copies; 35.5 × 28cm.). (Box 24)
  - 51. Woman with basket of flowers., Carbro print on thin paper. (27.5 × 23cm.). (Box 24)
  - 52. Semi-nude woman holding horse from a carousel., Dye imbibition. (32.2 × 25cm.). (Box 24)
  - 53. Red flowers in vase on plaid cloth., Carbro print (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 54. Geraniums., Dye imbibition (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 55-56. Child with cup, 1934.; Dye imbibition (2 copies, color variation; no.55: 25 × 33.5, no.56: 27.5 × 35cm.). (Box 24)
  - 57. Store mannequins., Dye print(?) on very thin paper (32 × 25.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 58-61. Old lady with quilt., (4 copies, various sizes). (Box 24)
  - 62. Model sunbathing. Analglyph experiment., (28 × 35.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 63. Valves of various sizes and colors., (35.5 × 27.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 64. Valves. Fragment of photograph no.63, cutout areas., (20.5 × 25.5cm.). (Box 24)
  - 65-79. Grace Brown's cut-outs. Paper dolls performing various activities., (15 photos; sizes vary). (Box 24)
  - 80. Unidentified photograph. Black background with dog-house shapes of various colors. Color wheel experiment(?)., (11.5 × 18cm.). (Box 24)
- Part Three, The following photographs are unmounted and are 35.1 × 27.7cm. (14 × 11) unless otherwise noted.; Compiled by Kayla Landesman and Hilda Bohem.
  Most photographs are not individually identified as in Part One, however Grace Connell identified some of the groups of photographs. No dates are given and there are multiple duplicates.
  - Miscellaneous advertising, including Bullocks Wilshire., 96 photos. (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous advertising; Big Bear Boys Camp., 116 photos. (Box 26)
  - Circus elephants., Most of these photographs have been mounted on boards. 36 photos. (Box 27)
  - Industrial views including applied physics., 110 photos. (Box 28)
  - Nutralite; Magicians; Miscellaneous advertising; Industrial views; Miscellaneous portraits., 105 photos. (Box 29)
  - Hughes Tool (2nd Employee Book); Oil; Industrial views., 96 photos. (Box 30)
  - California scenery; Fashion advertising; Miscellaneous advertising; Trick photography., 102 photos. (Box 31)
  - Trick photography; Montages; Music., Sizes of photographs vary in this box, some are cut-outs. 85 photos. (Box 32)
  - Pomona College; Unidentified architectural views (includes interiors of homes)., 118 photos. (Box 33)
  - Oil; Architectural Views, Including the Following:
    - Bullocks Wilshire. (Box 34)
    - Zacho's, Wilshire Boulevard. (Box 34)
    - By Lloyd Wright:
      - Derby House, Chevy Chase, Glendale. (Box 34)
      - Taggart House, Griffith Park. (Box 34)
      - Sowden House, Franklin Avenue, Hollywood. (Box 34)
      - Samuel-Navarro House, Los Angeles. (Box 34)
      - Yucca-Vine Market, Hollywood. (Box 34)
      - Project Model. (Box 34)
      - Ennis House., 94 Photos. (Box 34)
  - Portraits of Motion Picture and Prominent Personalities, Including the Following:
    - George Arliss. (Box 35)
    - Joan Bennett. (Box 35)
    - James Cagney. (Box 35)
    - Myrna Loy. (Box 35)
    - William Powell. (Box 35)
    - Ida Lupino. (Box 35)
    - Greer Garson. (Box 35)
    - Paulette Goddard. (Box 35)
    - Walt Disney. (Box 35)
    - Loretta Young. (Box 35)
    - Lionel Stander. (Box 35)
    - Shirley Temple. (Box 35)
    - Jean Harlow. (Box 35)
    - W.C. Fields. (Box 35)
    - Al Jolson. (Box 35)
    - Ginger Rogers. (Box 35)
    - Constance Cummings. (Box 35)
    - Alice Faye. (Box 35)
    - Bing Crosby. (Box 35)
    - Yehudi Menuhin. (Box 35)
    - Fujita. (Box 35)
    - Lloyd Wright. (Box 35)
    - Rockwell Kent. (Box 35)
  - Will Connell Studio (exterior view); Yale Puppets., Photographs mounted and overmatted for the exhibit, either 55 × 45.5cm. or 45.5 × 55cm. 104 photos. (Box 35)
    The following photographs were on exhibit at San Francisco Museum of Modern Art September 25-November 6, 1981. All but the first eight from Box 36 were removed from Boxes 1-24 listed in Part One of this register.
  - 1. Myrna Loy, n.d.; (35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 36)
  - 2. Untitled. Wheels for a Lockheed aircraft, n.d.; (32.7 × 26cm.). (Box 36)
  - 3. Untitled. Dynamotor, n.d.; (35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 36)
  - 4. The P-38 Line, 1943.; (25.2 × 33cm., mounted: 27.2 × 34.5cm.). (Box 36)
  - 5. Untitled. Richfield thermal crusher, n.d.; (35.4 × 37.8cm.). (Box 36)
  - 6. Untitled. Man's oxford shoes, n.d.; (35.5 × 28.2cm.). (Box 36)
  - 7. Pewter & glass table designed by Kem Weber, n.d.; (35 × 27.9cm.). (Box 36)
  - 8. Myrna Loy, William Powell & Asta, n.d.; (35 × 27.5cm.). (Box 36)
  - 9. Assembly line, Douglas plant, 1936. (Box 36)
  - 10. Wings, 1936. (Box 36)
  - 11. Golden Gate Bridge: Sodium lamp, 1937. (Box 36)
  - 12. Untitled. Train inside the San Bernadino Roundhouse (Engine no.7855) (Box 36)
  - 13. Colton, 1937. (Box 36)
  - 14. Necktie and fabric swatches, 1931. (Box 36)
  - 15. Wine goblet, 1936. (Box 36)
  - 16. 335. Standard Refinery, Kettleman [California], 1931. (Box 36)
  - 17. Lorraine (?) towers at Standard well in the North dome, Kettleman Hills [California] field, 1931. (Box 36)
  - 1. Refinery, 1931. (Box 37)
  - 2. Top view of Mission Day bottles showing various flavors, 1930. (Box 37)